Vacant Possession is a drama film directed by Margot Nash.
Following the death of her mother, a young woman returns after many years to the
weather-beaten family home on the shores of Sydney's Botany Bay.
But the old family home begins to bring old wounds more and more to life.
The story unfolds through flashbacks yet as it progresses the flashbacks merge into the present as it becomes
apparent that the situation Tessa has returned to is very much the result of that which passed before.
Tessa, played by Pamela Rabe.
Frank, played by John Stanton.
Joyce, played by Toni Scanlan.
Kate, played by Linden Wilkinson.
Auntie Beryl, played by Rita Bruce.
Millie, played by Olivia Patten.
Vacant Possession is a 1995 Australian drama film directed and written by
Margot Nash and starring Pamela Rabe and John Stanton.
The film was nominated for 5 awards at the 1995
Australian Film Institute Awards.
The tone is emotional.